[
  {
    "question": "Which year was Obama born",
    "answer_a": "1967",
    "answer_b": "1955",
    "answer_c": "1961",
    "answer_d": "1971",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 10000 milliliters",
    "answer_a": "1 L",
    "answer_b": "10 L",
    "answer_c": "100 L",
    "answer_d": "1000 L",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The cow says...",
    "answer_a": "Muu",
    "answer_b": "Quack",
    "answer_c": "it says nothing",
    "answer_d": "Mumbles",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which letter i missing?",
    "answer_a": "T",
    "answer_b": "S",
    "answer_c": "N",
    "answer_d": "Q",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many irishmen in a bar?",
    "answer_a": "1",
    "answer_b": "2",
    "answer_c": "3",
    "answer_d": "over 100",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Christiania located?",
    "answer_a": "Sweden",
    "answer_b": "Norway",
    "answer_c": "Denmark",
    "answer_d": "Germany",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a strawberry?",
    "answer_a": "A fruit",
    "answer_b": "A nut art",
    "answer_c": "its meat",
    "answer_d": "Vegetables",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time of the day is 7pm",
    "answer_a": "Morning",
    "answer_b": "Afternoon",
    "answer_c": "Night",
    "answer_d": "Evening",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Spot the non-president guy",
    "answer_a": "James Madison",
    "answer_b": "John Quincy Adams",
    "answer_c": "Zachary Taylor",
    "answer_d": "Thomas Edison",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lord of the....",
    "answer_a": "Chickens",
    "answer_b": "Holy Street Performer",
    "answer_c": "Rings",
    "answer_d": "Castle",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many legs does a spider have",
    "answer_a": "4",
    "answer_b": "8",
    "answer_c": "7",
    "answer_d": "9",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many pieces are there in chess",
    "answer_a": "32",
    "answer_b": "16",
    "answer_c": "36",
    "answer_d": "42",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many continents in the world?",
    "answer_a": "6",
    "answer_b": "7",
    "answer_c": "8",
    "answer_d": "9",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long was the Gulf War?",
    "answer_a": "3 Years",
    "answer_b": "2 Years",
    "answer_c": "1 Year",
    "answer_d": "About 6 Months",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people live in Brazil",
    "answer_a": "209 Millions",
    "answer_b": "170 Millions",
    "answer_c": "260 Millions",
    "answer_d": "300 Millions",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Lebanon",
    "answer_a": "Bern",
    "answer_b": "Beirut",
    "answer_c": "Bissau",
    "answer_d": "Oslo",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 Foot in meters",
    "answer_a": "about 1 meter",
    "answer_b": "about 2 meters",
    "answer_c": "about 3 meters",
    "answer_d": "about 4 meters",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "46 * 77 =?",
    "answer_a": "2942",
    "answer_b": "3842",
    "answer_c": "4277",
    "answer_d": "3542",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  }
]